

### About Me

Monu kr. shaw, a full-stack web developer & UI designer working remotely around the world. I create websites. I'm passionate about building & designing delightful experiences with the combination of UI/UX design to make users satisfied when theyre using products and services online.

#### Contact

- Kolkata , WB 700060
- premraj00071@gmail.com
- +919038130362
- https://monushaw.github.io/portfolio

## Education

2021 - 2023

BCA

IGNOU

2018 - 2020

**Higher Secondary** 

G.B.M.I

# Monu Kr. Shaw

FullStack | MERNStack Developer

#### **Experience**

**NEXENTURE PVT. LTD** - Web Developer Intern

June 2022 - August 2022

 Manages Company Ongoing Projects And frequently Updating projects as requirement.

#### **Projects**

RICEDAILY.GA (E-COM) - Web Developer

Nov 2021 - Present

 Build Full Fledge E-Commerce Project using Php (Mysql) & Html,Js

#### **Experience**

PORTFOLIO TEMPLATE - React. Js Dev.

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- Builded During My Internship a moder portfolio template with react.js.
- for more visit my portfolio link

#### **Professional Skills**

| Javascript/ES6 | • | • | • | • | • | • |
|----------------|---|---|---|---|---|---|
| HTML           | • | • | • | • | • | • |
| CSS/Scss       | • | • | • | • | • | • |
| React.Js       | • | • | • | • | • | • |
| Php            | • | • | • | • | • | • |
| MySql/MongoDB  | • | • | • | • | • | • |

#### Interests

Gaming Traveling Reading

CP